<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Billy Okal</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Billy Okal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 23:14:46 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 12:00:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>You can find an up to date list of my publications on Google Scholar
 B. Okal and K. O. Arras, “Learning socially normative robot navigation behaviors with Bayesian inverse reinforcement learning,” in Proc. of IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA), May 2016. B. Okal, R. Triebel, and K. O. Arras, “Real-time social activity detection for mobile service robots,” in Proc. of IEEE International Symposium on Robot and Human Interactive Communication (RO-MAN), August 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Blogging</title>
      <link>/post/back-to-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 23:14:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/back-to-blogging/</guid>
      <description>So I after almost a decade hiatus, I decided to get back to writing blogs again. This is in part triggered by trying to learn new languages in elixir/erlang and rust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 23:08:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I am currently at 6 River Systems (a Shopify company) working on all things robotics for application in fulfillment. See more about our robots, called Chucks here.
Previously, I was at Voyage Auto building decision making ingredients (behavior planning, predictions and remote discrete assistance) for autonomous driving, and before that, I was at Apple SPG building autonomous systems. Prior to venturing into industry, I was an academic conducting research on normative navigation behaviors for mobile service robots at the University of Freiburg as part of my PhD studies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
